this maca shag show what's up with it
shout-out Ganesh vapes man they hooked
us up over the holidays reached out to
us and wanted to support the show hook
this up with some grinders if we got
some [\h__\h] baked pins nice new
packaging and also the one and only
goodness vapes email yeah what you got
bro I got the new silver lamp kit comes
in this fancy ass [\h__\h] zip up nice
yeah bursting right off the bat it has a
silicone dab container so your dad's in
it looks like a little bouncy ball back
in the 90s it's got battery they get 5
times on to turn it on five times off to
turn it off it's got a dual quartz coil
which is also replaceable saucy included
in the kit also comes with an extra
spare coil just in case it comes with a
charger port the awesome thing about
getting Nash's they charge on the side
of the battery you don't got the classic
school which is good too
you know on the side and it comes with a
dab tool so you're just gonna load like
a grain of rice with onto the dual
quartz coils in inside dad is definitely
bigger than a green it's like a long
grain yes sir
well I wouldn't recommend it doing it
inside this pin because it could flood
it and
including Ganesh vidcom by the coil
attachments separately eaten by the
atomizer even by the batteries civilan
klo - I don't get that vase man for sure
also I want to point out this real quick
they also have the air vents on the side
get a bigger or smaller hit like a 15
second hold on that baby yeah you can
just like a DAB just as fast as that was
this email is already heated up that's
about a minute that's that to get it to
550 so I'm gonna titanium nail I don't
want it too hot but also I want it too
low right now see I got some honey tree
this is uh bode highs honey tree
extracts real good [\h__\h] saucy smells
poopy everything
I'm gonna bump it up 6:10
that's usually what I hit you just push
this Harrow up get that nice big head
see just leave it that stress balls
goodness faves
hi lattice pine queen dream super piney
flavor I just really wanted to try off
that you know I've been doing out the
bait
and this is hella tasty hello earth e
hello tiny Terps are crazy out of it and
it's cheap oil to really good quality
Wow clearly we're getting way too high
great goodness product you guys go reach
out and buy it
Ganesh vapes calm this is great stuff
y'all might want to tap in on this my
name is Mack mr. Mack you sack show yep
follow me on instagram at Shack 101 and
follow me on Instagram the official mac
ty you can follow both of us to on the
Mac and Shaq TV
[Music]